(chuckles):
And-and here we are.
(Amy:)So, Sheldon and Bernadette
are hanging out.
(Howard:)I know. What are they
gonna talk about?
(laughs)
(Bernadette:)I don't know.
(Amy:)I really don't know.
(Penny:)Hey.
Oh, good!
Oh, thank God!
(Penny:)You guys been here long?
(Howard:)No, two minutes.
(Amy:)But yes.
(Howard:)Where's Claire?
(Raj:)Oh, she's meeting us here.
Hey, guys, do me a favor
and don't ask too many questions
(Raj:)about the relationship.
(Raj:)We're just keeping it casual.
(Leonard:)Oh, so I shouldn't ask her
how she feels about being
(Leonard:)a member of your harem?
(Raj:)Yeah, I know you're teasing,
but watch out for karma.
(Amy:)Hey, Penny, isn't that
your old boyfriend Zack?
(Howard:)Oh, yeah.
(Amy:)Are you gonna
say hi to him?
(Penny:)Uh, I don't know.
(Raj:)Hey, while you decide,
who was better in bed:
(Raj:)big hot Zack
or wheezy little Leonard?